<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/gsoc2024-Prajyot_Jadhav/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/gsoc2024-Prajyot_Jadhav/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en" /><updated>2024-05-23T15:34:08+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/gsoc2024-Prajyot_Jadhav/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Prajyot Jadhav | JdeRobot x GSoC 2024</title><entry><title type="html">Community Bonding: May 6 ~ May 19</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/gsoc2024-Prajyot_Jadhav/blog/2024/community-bonding-week-1-and-2/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Community Bonding: May 6 ~ May 19" /><published>2024-05-22T22:10:16+05:30</published><updated>2024-05-22T22:10:16+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/gsoc2024-Prajyot_Jadhav/blog/2024/community-bonding-week-1-and-2</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/gsoc2024-Prajyot_Jadhav/blog/2024/community-bonding-week-1-and-2/"><![CDATA[<p>I’m excited to be working with the JdeRobot community on the Robotics-Academy project. Google Summer of Code begins with a community bonding period, during which we familiarize ourselves with the community and explore the project to gain a better understanding.</p>

<h4 id="objectives">Objectives</h4>

<ul class="task-list">
  <li class="task-list-item"><input type="checkbox" class="task-list-item-checkbox" disabled="disabled" checked="checked" />Set up blog website using Jekyll and Github Pages</li>
  <li class="task-list-item"><input type="checkbox" class="task-list-item-checkbox" disabled="disabled" checked="checked" />Write a first blog for the community bonding period</li>
</ul>

<p>This week, we had our first official meeting where we introduced ourselves and the mentors reviewed the program’s logistics. In addition to my project mentors, I also got to know the other contributors selected for GSoC 2024 JdeRobot, as well as other members of the organization.</p>

<p>Before the official start of GSoC, I had already been using Robotics-Academy. I contributed by opening GitHub issues and submitting pull requests (<a href="https://github.com/JdeRobot/RoboticsAcademy/pull/2462">#2462</a>, <a href="https://github.com/JdeRobot/RoboticsAcademy/pull/2460">#2460</a>). These contributions were for the RADI version 3.x.x, which is based on ROS Noetic.</p>

<p>Also, the GSoC 2024 Contributor Summit was organized by the GSoC team. It included talks on AI and open source, security, OSS licensing, and diversity, equity, and inclusion (DEI), followed by Q&amp;A sessions with the speakers. It was an informative and inspiring event for all the participants.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Week 1 and 2 of the community bonding period]]></summary></entry></feed>